<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on BloxTop</title>
    <link>https://bloxtop.github.io/tags/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on BloxTop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 21:15:15 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bloxtop.github.io/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BTC short trade</title>
      <link>https://bloxtop.github.io/home/2020-02-09-btc-short-trade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 21:15:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloxtop.github.io/home/2020-02-09-btc-short-trade/</guid>
      <description>BTC short trade BTC shows weak today and reaches the resistance 10350. I&amp;rsquo;m not saying the bullish is over, but at leat a short-term pullback may appear. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s time to short.
Past performance does not guarantee future results. We are not investment advisors and do not provide investment or financial advice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTC long trade 2</title>
      <link>https://bloxtop.github.io/home/2020-02-06-btc-long-trade-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 10:15:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloxtop.github.io/home/2020-02-06-btc-long-trade-2/</guid>
      <description>BTC long trade 2 Previously on BTC long trade: It has broken the resistance strongly. Long opportunity may continue after a pullback in near future. It seems have gone the way as we expected. It raised to 9553 on 2020/01/31 and pullback to 9088 on 2020/02/05, then raised again(long opportunity).
Next step Now BTC is testing 9552, another wave is around the corner if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t break the support. I&amp;rsquo;m still bullish about future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SERO wait and long trade</title>
      <link>https://bloxtop.github.io/home/2020-01-30-sero-wait-and-long-trade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 17:18:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloxtop.github.io/home/2020-01-30-sero-wait-and-long-trade/</guid>
      <description>SERO wait and long SERO has broken the resistance 0.08. Long oppornity exists after a pullback. Let&amp;rsquo;s wait and long.
News and Events  Origo will burn 15% of total OGO supply. According to the recent blog post Origo has just burned 5% of total supply and will burn eventually another 10% during unspecified period of time. The tokens will come from from the Ecosystem Reserve (90M OGO) and from the Foundation Reserve (60M OGO).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTC long trade</title>
      <link>https://bloxtop.github.io/home/2020-01-28-btc-long-trade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 23:58:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloxtop.github.io/home/2020-01-28-btc-long-trade/</guid>
      <description>BTC long trade It has broken the resistance strongly. Long opportunity may continue after a pullback in near future.
News and Events  Top 5 most discussed new coins in Twitter year to date: BTT, BOLT, MATIC, ATOM, WIN. Top 5 most mentioned exchanges in Twitter year to date: Binance, Kucoin, Coinbase, Bitmex, Poloniex. Token sale detail of WazirX launches on Binance Lauchpad.   Past performance does not guarantee future results.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>