<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>others on BloxTop</title>
    <link>https://bloxtop.github.io/tags/others/</link>
    <description>Recent content in others on BloxTop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 11:19:15 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bloxtop.github.io/tags/others/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Halving year</title>
      <link>https://bloxtop.github.io/posts/2020-02-20-halving-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 11:19:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloxtop.github.io/posts/2020-02-20-halving-year/</guid>
      <description>Halving year Halving is a process of reducing the rate sending to miners when cryptocurrency is generated. There are some large Capitalization coins halving this year and they show great influence on cryptocurrency marcket. Here are some halvings you should know: Is the end of BTC bullish? BTC pullback came as expected and 10% dropped since 2020/2/13. Alts are slumping during the period. I can&amp;rsquo;t help to ask that does the BTC bullish end?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons learned</title>
      <link>https://bloxtop.github.io/posts/2020-02-12-lessons-learned/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 21:45:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloxtop.github.io/posts/2020-02-12-lessons-learned/</guid>
      <description>Day trading and lessons learned order to increase fund utilization, today I tried day trading and felt sucks for my operation. It&amp;rsquo;s quite different from what I usually do. it&amp;rsquo;s more vulnerable and having less time to think. Need to enter when chance come and get out when wrong immediately. Yellow line shows where I get in and out. It&amp;rsquo;s obvious not right to hold so long during day trading and no operation when finding enter the wrong position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Altcoin watch list</title>
      <link>https://bloxtop.github.io/posts/2020-02-07-altcoin-watchlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 18:50:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bloxtop.github.io/posts/2020-02-07-altcoin-watchlist/</guid>
      <description>Altcoin watchlist    Ticker Position Comment     STX out of bottom wait for a pullback   BAT reach resistance short-term distribution area may form   IOTA reach area 0.247~0.38 first wave of rally   BTT top sold, wait for buy back   wait for update wait for update wait for update    Past performance does not guarantee future results. We are not investment advisors and do not provide investment or financial advice</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>